Contact

+919848398458 (Mobile) rajesh_pdtr@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ rajeshkethepalle (LinkedIn) www.youtube.com/watch (Other) blogs.oracle.com/jobsatoracle/ (Other) www.oracle.com/in/index.html (Other)

Top Skills

Technical Recruiting Talent Management Recruiting

Rajesh Kethepalle

Build your career in Oracle on Cloud Technologies - Looking for Java UI Architects - Bengaluru/Hyderabad

Andhra Pradesh

Summary

Looking for passionate recruiters who would like to build career in recruitment. Professionals with experience 4 to 8 years and interested to work from Hyderabad/Bengaluru can share their resume to me on rajesh.kethepalle@oracle.com

Principal Talent Advisor

Oracle India Pvt Ltd Campus Phase 1 Hitech City Layout Madhapur Hyderabad - 500 081

Contact No: + 91 (40) - 6605 2894/6724 6802

Email: rajesh.kethepalle@oracle.com, rajesh_pdtr@yahoo.com

Twitter:@rajeshkethepall

Experience

Oracle
Principal Talent Advisor

September 2016 - Present (4 years)

Hyderabad

Oracle India Pvt Ltd

10 years

Looking for 4 to 8 years exp recruiters for Bengaluru location. July 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months)

Senior Recruiter September 2010 - Present (10 years) For more than three decades, Oracle has been the center of innovation for business software—birthplace of the first commercially available relational database, the first suite of Internet-based applications, and the next-generation enterprise-computing platform, Oracle Fusion.

Today, with more than 380,000 customers—including 100 of the Fortune 100—and with deployments across a wide variety of industries in more than 145 countries around the globe, Oracle offers an optimized and fully integrated stack of business hardware and software systems. Oracle engineers hardware and software to work together in the cloud and in the data center—from servers and storage, to database and middleware, through applications.

Our more than 120,000 global employees are critical to that success – read on and find out how you can be part of this success.

I am playing a pivotal role for building various product teams from scratch. I Partner with Business to handle recruitment needs for various products like Fusion, EBIZ, PGBU, HSGBU, Oracle Commerce.I understand customer needs and tweak my recruiting strategy to fulfill their needs in short time. I handle recruitment for multiple locations - Hyderabad, Bangalore & Noida.

Recruiter

September 2010 - Present (10 years)

For more than three decades, Oracle has been the center of innovation for business software—birthplace of the first commercially available relational database, the first suite of Internet-based applications, and the next-generation enterprise-computing platform, Oracle Fusion.

Today, with more than 380,000 customers—including 100 of the Fortune 100—and with deployments across a wide variety of industries in more than 145 countries around the globe, Oracle offers an optimized and fully integrated stack of business hardware and software systems. Oracle engineers hardware and software to work together in the cloud and in the data center—from servers and storage, to database and middleware, through applications.

Our more than 120,000 global employees are critical to that success – read on and find out how you can be part of this success.

As a Recruiter I handle recruitment for different product verticals. I am hired professionals in Java & J2EE, C, ASP.Net, VB.Net, PL SQL, Manual Testing, Automation, Oracle Applications functional.

Avaya India Pvt Ltd
Recruiter
September 2007 - August 2010 (3 years)
Hyderabad Area, India

Avaya Inc. designs, builds and manages communications networks for more than 1 million businesses worldwide, including 90 percent of the FORTUNE 500®. Focused on businesses large to small, Avaya is a world leader in secure and reliable Internet Protocol (IP) telephony systems and communications software applications and services.

Driving the convergence of voice and data communications with business applications - and distinguished by comprehensive worldwide services - Avaya helps customers leverage existing and new networks to achieve superior business results.

I was instrumental and played a key role in Building Avaya, Hyderabad center. I joined when it was 50 professionals and ramped up to 400 professionals. I hired professionals from Software Engineer to Sr.Management level. I handled lateral and fresher recruitment. Lateral hiring I did for telecom & technology professionals. I did campus and off campus recruitments. I hired professionals from ISB for Business Analyst positions.

I got many awards from Business for my end less support in building the organisation.

Intelligroup, Inc
Senior Executive - Recruitment
February 2005 - September 2007 (2 years 8 months)

The company was incorporated in New Jersey in October 1987 under the name Intellicorp, Inc. to provide systems integration and custom software development services. The company's name was changed to Intelligroup, Inc. in July 1992.

In June 2010, NTT Data Corporation of Japan bought Intelligroup in an all-cash tender offer for 100% of Intelligroup shares.

Intelligroup employs over 2,500+ professionals worldwide and has operations in the Americas, Europe, India, Middle East, Asia Pacific and Japan.

Intelligroup, Inc. is a vertically led global Information Technology ("IT") services organization and a leading provider of consulting, business optimization, and outsourcing solutions. The company provides end to end services including advisory, implementation, testing and application management and support services ("AMS") of Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) solutions from SAP AG, and Oracle Corporation including PeopleSoft. It also provide e-business solutions using Java and the Microsoft .NET platforms, Verification, Validation & Testing and infrastructure management services.

I played a instrumental role in building EBIZ team in Hyderabad & Bangalore. EBIZ team grown from 100 to 250 professionals in my tenure. I played a critical role by building teams in short time for various projects which increased the revenues of the of the group. I hired professionals for various technologies like Java, .Net, Sharepoint, Navision, QA professionals. I joined as Executive and got promoted to Senior Executive in Recruitment and Operations with Intelligroup Asia Pvt Ltd.

Tata Consultancy Services

Recruiter

June 2003 - February 2005 (1 year 9 months)

TCS is a leader in the global marketplace and among the top 10 technology firms in the world. Our continued rapid growth is a testament to the certainty our clients experience every day. Building on more than 40 years of experience, we add real value to global organizations through domain expertise plus solutions with proven success in the field and world-class service. It's how we keep you moving forward.

TCS offers a consulting-led integrated portfolio of IT and IT-enabled services delivered through its unique Global Network Delivery Model™ (GNDM™), recognized as the benchmark of excellence in software development.

TCS is part of the Tata group, one of India's largest industrial conglomerates and most respected brands.

TCS was established in 1968 as a division of Tata Sons Limited. TCS Ltd. got incorporated as a separate entity on January 19, 1995.

I worked as a Recruiter handling both lateral and fresher recruitment. For lateral recruitment I played a crucial role by building teams for various accounts, I hired for various technologies and domains.

I was part of campus and off campus recruitment team. I traveled to various colleges to do campus recruitment's. For off campus recruitment i handled large events consisting of more than 2000 plus candidates and made a huge success by hiring huge no's.

Education

Bangalore University
MBA, Human Resources · (1999 - 2001)

Bangalore University
BBM, Marketing · (1996 - 1999)